CURRICULUM VITAE



NAME: KRIPANIDHAN GUPTA

ADDRESS: VILL TIWARIPUR POST BARIPUR

P.O: SIKARIGANJ

Mobile no: +91- 9936756573

DIST: GORAKHPUR

Email.kripanidhan1@gmail.com

PIN: 273213

CAREER OBJECTIVE:

I would like to be associated with an organization to undertake challenging and responsible job where my education, skills, ability will be applicable and keep knowledge updated with the new trends.

SUMMARY:

Seeking challenging opportunities in execution & construction in civil engineering projects in leading construction/mining/design consultants based company preferably in northern, North region in india

TECHNICALQUALIFICATION:

B.TECH IN CIVIL ENGINEERING

WORK EXPERIENCE:

Organization: VERMA ASSOCIATE PVT Ltd.

Designation : Site Incharge- from june 2019 to Oct 2020

Project-1 : Shaheed Asfaq Ullah Khan pari udyan (Gorakhpur zoo).

<u>Client</u> U.P. Rajkiya Nirman Nigam Pvt Limited.

<u>Description</u>: Augmentation of existing with an area of 121.342 acres Zoo Gorakhpur. Approximatly 0.800 Mtr Road Two

Lan Road With Highrise Building and Dom Approach, Gorakhpur Zoo.

<u>Time Period</u>: June 2019 to April 2020.

Activities : Heading & Benching excavation by JCB Using Drilling patterns as per drawing and the rock condition fome work Brickwork, mortar plaster with 6&12mm internal external wall with slav palsterin slab rcc sloping slab casting as drawing, conduit work checking copper wire steel with chair and covers block also slab labeling as per drawing With fixing rood from and window frame as pr drawing Also fixing rood and windows Checking location of cupboard and chajja, Checking sanitary work with material And location of fixing all sanitary items, Plinth level With Network of Beem and columm junction, checking road level from plinth checking location of Staircase, checking location of ventilator, quality of painting work checking quality of Titles, brick aggregate, course sand and river sand also steel etc.

Responsibility: Execution of activities as per drawing, Pilling contractor handling and contractor bill reinforcementJoint measurement sheets; manage materials and manpower at site, prepare & maintains MBs of each work, ensure a safety culture at site..

Project-2; Dr. Mukhtar Ansari District Hospital Ghazipur (200 Bed)

Client; U.P. Rajkiya Nirman Nigam Pvt Limited.

<u>Description</u>: Augmentation of existing with high rise Bilding.

Time Period; May 2020 to tell date.

Activities : Heading & Benching excavation by using JCB, PILLING Using hydraulic machin as per

Drowing and rock condition, etc.

Responsibility: Execution of activities as per drawing, Pilling contractor handling and contractor bill reinforcementJoint neasurement sheets; manage materials and manpower at site, prepare & maintains MBs of each work, ensure a safety culture at site...

Organization: Krishna construction Pvt ltd

CURRICULUM VITAE

Activities: Heading & Benching excavation by using JCB, PILLING Using hydraulic machin as per

Drowing and rock condition, etc.

Responsibility: Execution of activities as per drawing, Pilling contractor handling and contractor bill reinforcementJoint measurement sheets; manage materials and manpower at site, prepare & maintains of each work, ensure a safety culture at site...

Project: Forensic Science Laboratory, Ghaziabad Uttar Pradesh.

Client U.P. Rajkiya Nirman Nigam Pvt Limited.

<u>Description</u>: Construction of heigh rise buildings with guest house and road.

<u>Time Period</u>: November 2018 to May 2019

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION:

Collage Name: DR.K.N. MODI INSTITUTE OF ENGINEERING AND TECHNOLOGY MODINAGAR

: UTTER PRADESH

:B.TECH in Civil Engineering in 2019 with 73.4% marks from DR. AKTU

SCHOOL NAME: M.P. INTER COLLAGE GORAKHPUR

:Passed Higher Secondary in 2013 with 71.4% mark from UTTER PRADESH BOARD

: Passed 10th in 2011 with 56.2 mark from Allahabad board

Computer Proficiency: knowledge of Autocard 2007, MS-Office MS-Word, MS-Excel, PowerPoint.

PERSONAL PROFILE:

Father's Name:Ram shri Gupta Date of Birth: 4th jan, 1996

Gender :Male.

Marital Status: Unmarried.
Nationality: Indian
Religion: Hindu.
Cast: O.B.C.

Strength : Motivating, Hardworking;

Ambition of Life: achieve every high levels of performance, to innovate ideas and gain knowledge and experience

On an ongoing basis in the field of Civil Engineering.

Language Known: English (Read, Write Speak), Hindi (Read, Write & Speak).

Hobbies : Drawing, Photo Editing, Video Editing, Photography

DECLARATION:

I KRIPANIDHAN GUPTA do	1 1 00 41 441	C	1	C 1 1 1 11 1' C
I KRIPANIDHAN GUPTA do	solemnly affirm that the	e facts provided are frije an	d geniiine to the best (of my knowledge and belief

Date:

Place: (Gorakhpur) Regards: Kripanidhan Gupta